{
    "id": "fe787bfb3425445f996e41ba56a54642",
    "title": "Would and Should Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "caac3eec2dee43cc80df2cba40e82e00",
            "title": "Should or Would | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Everybody ............................. wear seat belts.",
                    "description": "We use should to talk about obligation. Would is not possible with this meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When we were kids, we ................................ spend hours playing football.",
                    "description": "To talk about past habits, we use 'would'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I told them we ................................ probably be late.",
                    "description": "In British English, with the first person pronouns I and we both would and should can be used to express simple futurity. Note that should is not normally used with this meaning in American English. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ................................ be grateful for an early reply.",
                    "description": "In British English, with the first person pronouns I and we both would and should can be used to express simple futurity. Note that should is not normally used with this meaning in American English. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "People ............................... drive more carefully.",
                    "description": "To express obligation, we use should.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................ you like something to eat?",
                    "description": "In polite offers and requests, we use 'would', not 'should'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Would",
                        "Should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................... we invite Mary?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Should",
                        "Would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ............................... not have called him a fool - it really upset him.",
                    "description": "We use 'should not have ' to refer to unwanted things that happened. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I knew that I ............................ write to her, but it seemed too difficult.",
                    "description": "We use 'should' to talk about obligations. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................. we call the police?",
                    "description": "In questions, should is used to ask for advice or instructions. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Should",
                        "Would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you ................................... behave like this?",
                    "description": "We use 'wish + would' to express ideas such as dissatisfaction or irritation. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "wouldn't",
                        "shouldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish it ............................. stop raining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}